Jason Hannanto

SOFTWARE ENGINEER · STUDEN

3001 Front St. Alhambra, CA 91803

🛮 (626) 267-6038 | 🗷 Hannanto@usc.edu | 🏕 www.JasonHannanto.github.io | 🖸 JasonHannanto | 🛅 JasonHannanto

Summary_

Hi! My name is Jason. I'm currently a sophomore at the University of Southern California pursuing a B.S in Computer Science. Creating and perfecting a smooth and exciting user experience on a digital platform is my craft and I'm always excited to learn about new methods and technologies to better develop solutions.

Education

University Of Southern California

Los Angeles, CA

B.S - COMPUTER SCIENCE Expected Graduation: 2020

Work Experience

USC Davis School of Gerontology

Los Angeles, CA

WEBMASTER

Aug 2017 - Present

- Management of online websites, content, and courses.
- · HTML, CSS, Wordpress, Blackboard

Reliant Pulmonary/Critical Care

Monterey Park, CA

Medical Scribe
Mar. 2016 - Aug 2017

- Complete realtime/retrospective charting of patient encounters, including History of Present Illness, Review of Systems, Past Medical History, Family/Social History, Assessment (ICD-10 coding)/Plan, Vitals, Diagnostic Tests, and Medications.
- Navigation/set-up of EHR/Radiographic Imaging software/programs
- Documentation/Transcription of Lab Results, Radiographic Imagery Reports, and procedural reports.

Projects

[Current] Music Lyric/Chord Management Web App

WEB APP ALLOWS USERS TO CREATE/STORE SONGS WITH CHORDS FOR LIVE PLAYING. FEATURES THE CAPABILITY TO TRANSPOSE

Aug 2017 - Present

- **KEYS LIVE. USED WEEKLY BY THE CHURCH MUSIC TEAM.** Working under a Senior Software Developer
- Debug posted issues / Refactor code for efficiency
- Develop new features for Web App

[Current] JasonHannanto.github.io

PORTFOLIO/RESUME WEBSITE Aug 2017 - Present

• Creating a visually appealing and responsive website

Skills_

Programming C++, Python

Frontend HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap

Backend Node.js, Express.js **Database** NoSQL, MongoDB

Version Control Git

Paradigms REST, OPP, Unit Testing